Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Pension Benefit Guarantee Corp., Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 26, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 14, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 29, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 27, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Valluation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 26, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 58: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 30, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 62: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Valuation Interst Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 13, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-MultiEmployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 65: PBGC Announces Maximum Guarantee for 1988, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 23, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 67: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 68: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 70: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 30, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 72: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 15, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 74: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 13, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. April 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: PBGC Issues Interim Rule on Paument of Pension Insurance Premiums, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 30, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 81: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: PBGC Issues Interim Rule on Payment of Pension Insurance Premiums, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. August 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 89: Interest Rate for Determination of Variable Rate Premium Amount, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 90: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 30, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. September 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 5, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 14, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. October 28, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Interest Rates and Quantities Used to Value Immediate and Deferred Annuities in Non-multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 98: Interest Rates for Valuing VestedBenefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. November 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. December 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 100: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. January 6, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 101: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. February 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Valuation Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 103: Late Payment Interest Rates, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. March 31, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 104: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 105: Interest Rates for Valuing Vested Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. May 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 106: Interest Rates for Valuing Vsted Benefits for PBGC's Variable Rate Premium, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 107: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 108: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 14, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 109: Letter from Judith E. Bekelman, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 110: Withdrawal Liability Interest Rate, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. June 30, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 111: 1989 Annual Premium Payment Package Pension Benefit Guaranty Corporation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    By Pension Benefit Guarantee Corporation. July 10, 1989. Item is in English.
- Pepsi-Cola Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Pepsi-Cola Company and the MBA, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    By Pepsi-Cola Company. Item is in English.
- Peterson Builders, Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employees Manual, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Peterson Builders, Inc. June 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Safety Manual, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    By Peterson Builders, Inc. May 1981. Item is in English.
- Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Pfizer Today: Bringing Science to Life, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Imagine Yourself at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Pfizer Scene, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. December 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: December 11, 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By PfizerPfizer Pulse Vol. 11 No. 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Report on Equal Opportunity Affairs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Welcome: A Handbook for Pfizer Headquarters Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Pfizer: A World of Choice, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Educational Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Summary of Pfizer Policies on Business Conduct, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: MBA Opportunities at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Pfizer Inc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Top Opportunity Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    By Pfizer. Februray 15, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Imagine Yourself at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Pfizer in Action: A Report on Corporate Responsibility, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Pharmaceutical Executive: A Business and Marketing Publication, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Employee Benefits Highlights, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Annual Report to Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Welcome to the World of Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Where Individuals Thrive, A Corporation Prosper, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Pfizer Facts Pharmaceutical Sales, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Our New Product Roll-Out is Under Way: Annual Report 1989, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Take a Closer Look at Your Future with Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Pharmaceutical Sales, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Take a Closer Look at Your Future with Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Pfizer Today, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Where Individuals Thrive, A Corporation Prospers, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Annual Report to Employees, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Welcome to the World of Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Welcome to the World of Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Imagine Yourself at Pfizer, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: An Equal Opportunity Employer: Career Opportunities, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Pfizer-Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Relocation Assistance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Employee Benefits Highlights, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Long Term Disability Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Employee Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Group Life and Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Letter from Personnel Representative, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Matching Gifts Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Retirement Annuity Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Service Award Program, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: 1982 Scholarship Awards: 1980 Qualifying Test, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: 25 Year Employee Service Award Program, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Supplemental Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Group Dental Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Business Travel Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Where Individuals Thrive, A Corporation Prospers, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Dupree, Richard Redwood, 1885-, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Call News: August September 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. August September 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Call News October 1980 No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Call News February 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Call News November 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Call News July 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Call News January 1980, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. March 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. April 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. December 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. Year End 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Call News No. 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. October 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. November 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. December 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. January 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. September 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. October 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. June/July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. February/ March 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. August 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. July 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. March 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. February 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Call News, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    By Philip Morris Incorporated. January/ February 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Philip Morris Companies Inc. Annual Report 1989, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Philips Petroleum Company, Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Career with a Future, Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
    By Phillips Petroleum Company. Item is in English.
- Pillsbury Company: Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Employee Performance Appraisal and Development Planning Guide, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    By Pillsbury Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Career Growth: We Have All the Ingredients, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: R&D Little Reporter, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    By Pillsbury Company. November 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action Programs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    By Pillsbury Company. September 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Professional Clerical/ Secretarial Development Schedule, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    By Pillsbury Company. January- June 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Management Development and Specialized Skills Schedule, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    By Pillsbury Company. january- June 1984. Item is in English.
- Pillsbury Co. - House Organs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Newsline Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    By Pillsbury Company. September 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newsline Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    By Pillsbury Company. April 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Reporter, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    By Pillsbury Company. March 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Reporter, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    By Pillsbury Company. February 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: eporter, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    By Pillsbury Company. January 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Pillsbury Inc. Fact Shet, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Pillsbury Inc. Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Pillsbury Inc. Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Pillsbury Brands, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Grand Metropolitan: Pillsbury Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Pittney-Bowes: Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Pitney Bowes Book of Paper-Handling Efficiency: A Concise Guide to the Components that make up the systems that save time and money in business paperflow, Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
    By Pittney-Bowes. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Benefits, Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
    By Pitney-Bowes. Item is in English.
- Pittney Bowes - House Organs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: PB News: Pitney Bowes' benefit payouts are no small chnge; See ways to profit you and PB too, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: PB News: O'Connell, Roney pitch new products (above) All in the Family, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: PB News: The Dangerous Day of Jim McAteer: Sales "action" reaches fever pitch, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: PB News: Bonnie loves Bracken, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: PB News: They work while most of us play, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Pittney Bowes - House Organs, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: PB News Vol. 18 No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. May 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: PB News Vol. 19 No. 4, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. June/ July 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: PB News Vol. 19 No. 5, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. August 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: PB News Vol. 19 No. 7, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: PB News Vol. 20 No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. April 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: PB News Vol. 20 No. 6, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. September 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: PB News Special Election Issue, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: PB News Vol. 20 No. 7, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. October 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: PB News Vol. 20 No. 8, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: PB News Vol. 21 No. 4, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. August 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: PB News Vol 21 No. 7, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. November 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: PB News Vol. 22 No. 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. January 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: PB News Vol. 22 No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. May 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Performance Management, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: The Pitney Bowes Suggestion System, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: PB News Vol. 22 No. 3, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    By Pitney Bowes. June/ July 1984. Item is in English.
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass: Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Fiber Glass: A Dream Fiber for a Dream Century, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    By Pittsburgh Plate Glass. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Romance of Glass, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: 1982 Learning Resources Directory, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: A Concern for Your Future, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    By Pittsburgh Plate Glass. February 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Highlights of Your PPG Industries Employee Savings Plan, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: PPG Products Vol. 89 No. 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: A Concern for Your Future: Careers with PPG Chemicals, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: PPG News Vol. 18 No. 11, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    By Pittsburgh Plate Glass. December 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Equal Employment Opportunity, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Corporate Objectives 1981, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Benefits: Your 1981 Personal Annual Statement of Benefits, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Group Insurance Plans for Hourly Employees of PPG Industries, Inc. Glass Division, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    By Pittsburgh Plate Glass. March 24, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Opportunities: Careers in Chemicals, Coatings and Resins, Fiber Glass, Glass, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Polaroid Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Polaroid Highlights Innovation at 54th Annual Meeting of Stockholders, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    By Polaroid Corporation. May 7, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Executive Profile, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    By Polaroid Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Polaroid Report on the Environment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)